双语制作：dahongying@CHD
感谢字幕原创者：南丁格尔
每个人都有一个天使
Everyone has an angel.
一个守护自己的天使
A guardian who watches over us.
我们不知道，他们会以什么样子出现
We can't know what form they’ll take.
今天是一个老人
One day, old man.
明天，可能就是一个小女孩
Next day, little girl.
不要让他们的外表欺骗了你
But don't let appearances fool you.
他们就像那些恶龙一样有害
They can be as fierce as any dragon.
但他们不会加入到我们战役中…
Yet they're not here to Fight our battles...
只是在我们的心里说…
but to whisper from our heart...
提醒这是我们自己
reminding that it's us.
正是我们自己掌控我们所创造的这个世界的力量
It's every one of us who holds the power over the worlds we create.
～有些人想要被利用～
～有些人想要虐待你～
～有些人想要被虐待～
不！
No!
不
No.
（最后的遗嘱 ）
（遗嘱：…我的一切留给我的两个女儿…）
～这是甜蜜的梦～
～我该是否认谁呢～
～穿越过全世界和七大洋～
～每个人都在寻找～
～有些人想利用你～
～有些人想被你利用～
～有些人想要虐待你～
～有些人想被虐待～
～有些人想要利用你～
～有些人想要被你利用～
～有些人想要虐待你～
～有些人想要被虐待～
片名：《美少女特攻队》
我们不能否认天使的存在
We can deny our angels exist...
说服自己相信，他们并非真实的
convince ourselves they can't be real.
但是他们总是以不同的方式出现
But they show up anyway.
出现在奇怪的地点
At strange places.
奇怪的时间
And at strange times.
他们可以通过我们想像不到的人对我说话
They can speak through any character we can imagine.
如果需要的话，他们甚至会扮成魔鬼…
They'll shout through demons if they have to...
警告我们…
daring us...
让我们鼓起勇气去战
challenging us to Fight.
（伦诺克斯 精神病院 ）
女性 20岁
Female. Age 20.
（暴力，对他人构成威胁）
（无法适应社会）
- 你是她的父亲？ - 继父
- You're the father? - Stepfather.
没错 我们通过电话了
That's right. We talked on the phone.
好，跟我来
Okay, come with me.
我带你们去“剧场”
We're gonna take her into the theater.
高斯基医生要看看她
Dr. Gorski's gonna want to take a look at her.
再带她去见见其他的女孩们
She likes to see all the new girls.
别担心，爸爸 会没事的
Don't worry, Dad. Everything's gonna be fine.
一切事情都在掌控之中
I've got everything under control around here.
好的 跟这我
Okay? Come on. Follow me.
这就是我们叫做“剧场”的地方
So this is what we call the theater.
骗子！
Liar!
女孩们 加油 加油
Oh, girls. Yes, go, go.
来这儿
Hey. Come here.
女孩 注意点
Girls. Behave.
- 都分开 都分开 - 你为何不阻止她们？
- Break it up. Break it up. - Will you stop them?
林恩
Lynn.
艾米
Amy.
坐下
Sit down.
坐
Sit.
总之，女孩们在这里进行社交活动的地方
Anyway. So the girls use this place to be social.
高斯基医生，她在那里帮助她们进行治疗
Dr. Gorski, she uses it to help them deal with their issues.
波兰疗法
Polish therapy.
很精彩的表演，接触到她们或者打她们的时候
It's quite a show, watching them act out who touched them or beat them.
高斯基医生觉得这样是有帮助的 可是我不这样以为
Dr. Gorski seems to think it helps. I'm not so sure.
但是不管有用还是没用 你都不需要担心了
But whether it does or doesn't won't matter much to you.
一旦我们处理了一点点的事情后…
Once we take care of a little bit of business...
- 就不再会有那样的情况了 - 很好
- ...there won't be any of that for this one. - Good.
她们就已经在天堂里了 如果你明白我的意思
She'll be in paradise, if you know what I mean.
并将结束你所有的问题，对吧？
And all of your troubles will be over.
我们在电话里讲好了是1400美元$
Now, I know we said 1400 on the phone ....
但是我在这里冒着很大的风险…
I'm taking a really big risk here...
所以你必须再给我2000美元
so it's gonna have to be 2 grand even.
你在说什么？不要想欺骗我，都说好了的
What the hell are you talking about? We had a deal.
听我说，父亲，我不会告诉你怎么做
Listen, Father, I'm not gonna tell you what to do.
很明显 你是一个人可以照顾好自己的人
Clearly you're a man that can take care of himself.
我不知道你对这个女孩做了什么 坦白地说，我也不想知道
I don't know what you did to this girl. And, frankly, I don't wanna know.
当警长来询问的时候你会准备说些什么呢？
What are you gonna tell the detectives when they come around?
我可以保证他们不会听信这个女孩的话
They're gonna love her side of the story.
- 是 - 好吧
- Yeah. - Okay.
我要开始放音乐了
I'm going to start your music.
你是安全的
You are safe.
非常安全
It's all safe.
放松点
Now relax.
忘掉一切
And just let go.
还有一件事：
Now, here's the other thing:
我们并没有能进行前脑叶白质切除术的职员
I don't have a doctor on staff who does lobotomies.
- 什么？ - 但是…
- What?   - But...
但是正好就有一个人预定会在五天之内到
there happens to be one scheduled to come in in five days.
我们可以伪造指纹，签名什么的 我已经做过很多次了
So I'll just forge her signature. I've done it a dozen times.
就像我们说过的
it's like we talk about.
你来控制这个世界
You control this world.
我给警察说她在母亲死后失去了理智
I told the police she lost her mind when her mother died.
事实是比这更复杂一点
The truth is a little more complicated.
忘掉那些痛苦
Let the pain go.
忘掉那些伤害
Let the hurt go.
忘掉那些愧疚感…
Let the guilt go.
你现在想象到什么…
What you're imagining right now...
那个你所控制的世界？
that world you control?
可以是一个没有痛苦的地方…
That place can be as real as any pain.
别让她记得这些事情
I don't want her to remember a thing.
别担心，在我们对她处理之后，她甚至都不记得自己的名字
Don't worry, she won't even remember her name when I'm done with her.
（如遇火灾，将打开所有的门）
停止！
Stop.
把那个给我拿开
Get that thing away from me.
快给我拿开
Get it away from me.
我的意识呢？
Where is my mind?
并且关掉这该死的音乐
And shut off that damn music.
松开这些
Undo these straps.
还有脚踝的
Don't forget my ankles.
快点！
Hurry.
有什么问题吗，香豌豆？
Is there a problem, Sweet Pea?
这是一个玩笑，对吗？
This is a joke, right?
你不明白这个剧情吗？
Don't you get the point of this?
这是为了骗别人的
It's to turn people on.
我是在扮演这个性感小女生
I get the sexy little schoolgirl.
我甚至在帮助 这些精神有问题的人们
I even get the helpless mental patient, right? That can be hot.
这些是什么呢？
But what is this?
做了脑叶切断术的植物人？
Lobotomized vegetable?
如果来一些更商业化的 你觉得怎么样呢？
How about something a little more commercial, for God's sakes?
香豌豆，你可以过来一下吗？
Sweet Pea, could you come here, please?
你一定要帮我
You gotta help me.
我是剧中的明星，记得吗？
I'm the star of the show, remember?
我会想想办法的
I'll figure something out.
好吧，各位，收拾吧！
All right, ladies. Wrap it up.
亲爱的香豌豆，我给你介绍一个人，这是…
Sweet Pea, I want you to meet somebody. This...
哦，别告诉我
Don't tell me.
神父把她从一个孤儿院带来的
The priest brought you here from the orphanage to lose your virginity, right?
如果换个说法
Oh, let me rephrase that.
就是出售
To sell it.
是啊，没错
Yeah, that's right.
多么独特啊
How original.
豪赌客将为她在这待5天
The High Roller is coming for her in five days.
他不久就会，你知道的，来一次采花行动
He's gonna, you know, just do a little flower picking.
并且他将会付出大价钱的
And he's gonna pay a lot of money for that.
你走运了
Luck you.
香豌豆你可以帮我个忙吗？
Can you do me a favor, honey?
你能带这个小宝贝豆到处逛逛
Can you show this little baby doll around,
陪她到机关内看看，好吗？
give her a tour of the establishment?
布鲁，你也看到节目了 我没有这个时间
Blue, you saw the show, okay? I don't have the time.
让我的姐妹来带她
Let my sister take her.
火箭女
Rocket.
带她到处看看吧
Show her around, will you, sis?
好吧，来，我们走吧
All right, come on. Let's go.
别担心，我又不会咬人
Don't worry, I don't bite very hard.
再见，我亲爱的
Goodbye, my dear.
天啊！
Jesus!
当豪赌客来了，你会得到报应的！
You'll get what you deserve when the High Roller comes!
- 冷静点 - 我没法冷静！
- Calm down. - I will not calm down.
- 你知道她做了什么？我希望你在这腐烂掉！ - 我知道 很抱歉
- You see what she did? I hope you rot! - I did. I'm sorry.
这边走
This way.
你会没事的 慢慢就会习惯了
You're gonna be okay. It just takes e little while to get used to.
那么，你是怎么变成一个孤儿呢？
So how'd you become an orphan?
哦，好吧，我知道了，很复杂对吗？
Oh, I get it. It's complicated, right?
我们心里都有自己的故事 我的故事…
Well, we all have our stories in here. Mine's...
很复杂
complicated
这间，是我们的接待室
These are the rooms where we take the clients.
浴室和更衣室在…
There's fresh towels in all the bathrooms and...
我工作的床
Turn that on.
布鲁是俱乐部的老板
Blue owns the club.
而我们呢，亲爱的，呵…
And we, my dear, heh...
是重要的吸引手段
are the main attractions. Ta-da.
这间俱乐部就是他们的生意
The club's a front for his business.
枪支、赌博、毒品以及特别的服务
Guns, gambling, medications, special favors.
他带来客户，我们负责让客户感到，你知道的…
He brings in his clients, and we gotta make them feel, you know...
特别服务
special.
新来的
New girl.
这是我们的后台
This is our backstage.
就算为了我们，不要带任何客户来这里了好吗？否则布鲁会发飙的
It's just for us, so don't bring any clients back here, okay? Or Blue's gonna get pissed.
清洗壁橱
Uh, cleaning closet.
你会找到拖把、扫帚、消毒水
You'll find all the mops, brooms, disinfectants.
新来的要承担清洗工作
New girls get cleaning duties.
我不是制定规则的
I don't make the rules.
如果你不愿按我说的做，布鲁会把我们关在这里…
And if you don't do what you're told, Blue locks us in here...
直到我们变得合作为止
until we become a bit more cooperative.
别担心，这不会发生在你身上的
Don't worry. it's not gonna happen to you.
这儿是厨房
This is the kitchen.
我们都在这里工作
We all work in here.
排演时间到了
Time for rehearsal.
- 她看上去挺好的 - 她看上去很奇怪
- She looked nice. - She looked stuck-up to me.
不，她只是很害怕
No. She's scared.
我很同情她
I feel sorry for her.
安布尔，你觉得每个人都很可怜
Amber, you feel sorry for everyone.
你还记得你第一次来到这里的时候？
Do you remember when you first got here?
可没人同情你
Nobody felt sorry for you.
但是对她别太过分了，好吗？
Well, don't get too attached to her, okay?
布鲁留着她是为了豪赌客
Blue's saving her for the High Roller.
她可不是处女
She's no virgin.
宝贝豆，那是安布尔，布女郎，你已经见过她了，香豌豆
Babydoll, that's Amber, Blondie, and you've met my sister, Sweet Pea.
- 看着点 - 各位，饶了她吧
- Watch yourself. - Come on, just give her a break.
她什么都没做呢
Yeah, she hasn't done anything to you guys.
她现在是你最好的朋友了吗？
You best friends now?
就让我介绍完这里的一切好吗？
Will you just let me finish my tour, please?
谢谢
Thank you.
每个人都要跳舞 以团队方式
Everybody gets a dance, a routine.
我们练习、练习、练习，然后这些人来看我们的表演
We practice, practice, practice, and the men come and watch us perform.
他们喜欢看的话…
And if they like what they see ....
那么今晚你就会看到了
Well, you'll see tonight.
晚上好，先生们
Good evening, gentlemen.
今晚我为你们准备了丰盛的东西
We've got a great night in store for you.
我发现那里有很多的新面孔
I see a lot of new faces out there.
同样也有一些熟悉的朋友
As well as some familiar ones.
那么我就不再多说废话了
So I'm not gonna yammer on too long.
请你们大家坐好放松，享受服务…
I want you all to sit back, enjoy the service...
…风景
the scenery.
但首先呢，欣赏这场表演
But most of all, enjoy the show.
对了
Hit it.
好吧
All right.
～这不是大不了的事～
it ain't no big thing
～等待着铃铛响起来～
To wait for the bell to ring
～这不是大不了的事～
It ain't no big thing
～把铃铛敲起来～
The toll of the bell
～剩余的时光没治了～
Aggravated, spare for days
～我在闹市的红灯区高声唱着～
I troll downtown The red light place
～跳啊 蹦啊 将要发生什么～
Jump up, bubble up What's in store
～爱是毒药 我必须得到～
Love is the drug And I need to score
～展示吧 展示吧 赶紧逃逸吧～
Showing out, showing out, Hit and run
～当男孩遇到女孩 节拍接着就变得～
Boy meets girl Well, the beat goes on
～越来越紧 我无法自由摇摆～
Stitched up tight I can't shake free
～因为爱对我来说就是毒药～
Because love is the drug for me
～爱是毒药～
Love is the drug
～那天很晚 我停好车～
Late that night I park my car
～沉迷于那个单身酒吧里～
Stake my place in the singles bar
～面对着面 脚尖对着脚尖～
Face to face, Toe to toe
～心贴着心 我们跺着地板～
Heart to heart as we hit the floor
～～
Lumber up, limbo down
～紧紧拥抱 打转跌倒～
The locked embrace, the stumble round
～我说走～
I say go
～我说好～
And I say yes
～暗淡的光线 分不清是谁～
Dim the lights, you can guess the rest
～爱是毒药～
Love is the drug
～爱是爱是毒药～
Love is Love is the drug
～对我来说爱是毒药～
Love is the drug for me
～噢，跟着感觉走～
Oh, catch that buzz
～因为爱是毒药 我想起来了～
Because love is the drug I'm thinking of
～你看不懂爱是毒药吗～
Can't you see Love is the drug
～把我魂儿勾去吧～
Got a hook in me
～跟着感觉走 因为爱是毒药 我想起来了～
Oh, catch that buzz Because love is the drug that I'm thinking of
～你看不懂爱对我来说是毒药吗～
Oh, can't you see Love is the drug for me
～没什么大不了 耶 没什么大不了～
Ain't no big thing Yeah, no big thing
～你看不懂爱对我来说是毒药吗～
Can't you see Love is the drug for me
～爱是毒药～
Love is the drug
～爱是 爱是～
Love is, love is
～爱是毒药～
Love is the drug
～毒药 毒药 爱是毒药～
Drug, drug. The drug is love.
那个给我
Give me that.
快来人！帮帮我！
Somebody! Help me!
快放手，蠢猪
Let her go, pig.
我什么都没做
I didn't mean nothing.
只是闹着玩的
Just having a little fun.
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah. Let's just go.
我不想迟到
We don't wanna be late.
一二三四，五六七八
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
二二三四，五六七八 停下
Two, two, three, four, arms, six, seven, eight. Stop.
停下！
Stop.
你的注意力在哪里？
Where are you right now?
你有用心吗？
Are you with us or not?
香豌豆，去休息一下吧
Sweet Pea, take break.
好吧
Yeah.
宝贝豆
Babydoll.
来
Come over here.
来、来
Come, come.
让我看看你
Let me look at you.
你看上去体型还不错
You seem fit enough.
我这就给你放点音乐
I'm going to play you some music, okay?
我希望你能放松
I want you to just relax. Feel the music.
打开你的心，感受音乐
Open your heart to it. Let it in.
当你准备好…
And when you are ready...
我希望你跳舞
I want you to dance.
如果你不跳舞，你就没什么价值
If you do not dance, you have no purpose.
我们不收留 没有价值的东西
And we don't keep things here that have no purpose.
如果你想为生存而战的话，现在就开始
You see, your fight for survival starts right now.
如果你不想被人批判 你就不会被批判
You don't want to be judged? You won't be.
你觉得你不够强壮吗？你很强壮
You don't think you're strong enough? You are.
你很害怕吗？完全没必要
You're afraid. Don't be.
你拥有所有你需要的武器
You have all the weapons you need.
现在开始战斗
Now fight.
再一次！
Again.
站起来
Stand up
你得设法控制
You've got to manage
喂？
Hello?
- 对不起，你能帮我吗？我… - 鞋子
- Excuse me, could you help me? I'm... - Shoes.
你说什么？
I'm sorry?
你的鞋子
Your shoes.
到处都是鞋子上的雪印
You're tracking snow everywhere.
哦，抱歉，我把它脱下来好吗？
Oh, I'm sorry. Should I take them off?
为时已晚
That time has passed.
我可以帮你什么呢？
What can I do for you?
没什么，我只是…
Nothing. I just...
让我换一个问法：
Let me ask it another way:
你在找什么？
What are you looking for?
一个出路 我猜
A way out, I guess.
你猜？
You guess?
不，我…
No, I...
我知道
I know.
我想要走出这里
I need to get out of here.
自由
Freedom.
并不是很难，不是吗？
That wasn't so hard, was it?
我会帮你获得自由
I'm going to help you to be free.
我要怎么做呢？
What do I have to do?
这些是你的武器
These are your weapons.
当你拿到它的时候，你就开始你的旅程
When you take them, you begin your journey.
你自由的征途
Your journey to freedom.
此行你要找齐五件东西
You will need five items for this journey.
首先是地图
The first is a map.
然后是，火、刀、钥匙
Then fire, a knife and a key.
你说是五件？
You said five things.
第五件是秘密
The fifth thing is a mystery.
是原因，目标
It is the reason. It is the goal.
会是一个重大的牺牲和完美的胜利
It will be a deep sacrifice and a perfect victory.
只有你能够找到
Only you can find it.
如果你找到的话
And if you do...
你就自由了
it will set you free.
最后一件事…
Oh, and one more thing:
保护好自己
Defend yourself.
那是什么？
What was that?
说真的，你应该教我如何像那样跳舞
Seriously, you're gonna have to teach me how to dance like that.
太狂热了
That was crazy.
真是太棒了 我喜欢摇摆
That was so amazing. I'm, like, shaking.
她让高斯基夫人跌破眼镜
I've never seen Madame Gorski clap like that before.
还是算了吧
Well, get over it.
就快熄灯了
It's nearly lights out.
她实在是太棒了
She's not easily impressed.
她并没有那么好 那些扭动和打斗
She wasn't impressed. All that gyrating and moaning.
舞蹈比这些更加丰富
The dance should be more than just titillation.
要更加私人一些 能够体现出个性
Mine's personal. It says who I am.
你的舞蹈都表现了什么？
What the heck does yours say?
表现出，我要离开这里
It says I'm gonna escape from here.
我会得到自由
That I'm gonna be free.
那记得从天堂寄一张明信片给我
Well, send me a postcard from paradise.
你真的准备从这里逃跑吗？
Are you really gonna try to escape?
是的，不然还能怎样
Yeah. Before the High Roller comes.
- 我可以一起吗？ - 我也是
- Can I come? - Me too.
- 当然可以 - 你那都不可以去，火箭女
- Yeah, of course. - You're not going anywhere, Rocket.
我要做我想做的事
I'm gonna do what I wanna do.
没有人可以从这里逃离 你们都知道的
No one's ever escaped from here. You know that.
是的 你知道上次有三个女孩因此丧生
Yeah. You know, the last three girls that tried died.
而且接下来，第四个女生也会发生一样的结果
And the same thing'll happen to the next fool.
为何不先听听我的计划？
Look, why don't you just listen to my plan?
我不想听你的计划，行吗？
Don't wanna hear your plan, okay?
任何人都不想听
None of us do.
现在开始准备，姑娘们
Now, let's get ready, girls.
排演在15分钟开始
Rehearsal in 15 minutes.
我们可不是需要帮助的孩子
We're not helping Baby.
- 听清楚了？ - 如果她有一个很好的计划呢？
- Am I clear? - What if it's a good plan?
那是他想到的
Then she can go through with it.
我不能让你受到伤害
I'm not letting you get hurt.
- 我要保证我们的安全 - 我知道你要怎么做
- I kept us safe through a lot of shit. - I know you have.
我也不想受伤
I'm not gonna get hurt.
我不能忍受，一直呆在这里
I just can't be here anymore.
如果那是个好计划，我们都一起走
And if it is a good plan, we're both going.
不，我们不去
No, we're not.
只有你自己
You're on your own.
我以前都没有一个人过
Well, I've been on my own before.
你当然有过
Sure you have.
看看都发生的什么
Look where that got us.
宝贝那天从厨师手里救了我
Baby saved me from the Cook the other day.
什么？
What?
当时我在厨房工作，然后他走到的我身后
I was working in the kitchen and he comes in behind me.
把我推倒在地上并爬到的我身上…
And he pushes me down and he gets on top of me...
我甚至无法动弹
and I can't even move.
这时候，她突然出现
And there she was, just like that.
而且把刀架在他的喉咙
She had a knife to his throat.
她救了我
She saved me.
（map地图 fire火 knife刀 key钥匙）
几天后就会有人过来
The High Roller comes for me in three days.
在他来之前，我就准备离开
But I'm getting out of here before he does.
如果想和我一起走的话 我们就实行计划
So if you guys wanna come with me, this is how I plan to do it.
怎样？
Well?
好吧
Okay.
如果能收集到这四件东西 我们将会获得自由
If we can collect all four of these items, we can be free.
好吧
Okay.
- 我们怎么用这些东西？ - 等等
- How do we use them? - Wait up.
一件件来
First things first.
你打算如何取得这些东西呢？
How do you plan on getting these things?
看谁有这些需要的东西 就找他过来看我跳舞
Well, whoever has the item we need, we get them to watch me dance.
当你跳舞，我们就去翻找他们的口袋？
While we run around and pick their pockets?
- 是的，没错 - 那我们就要冒很大的风险
- Yeah, that's right. - But we'd be taking all the risk.
我们要做所有的事 而你只是在那跳舞？
We'd be doing the work while you prance around with an alibi.
不. 只要我在那跳舞 他们就不会注意到你们
No. As long as I'm dancing, they won't even know you're there.
好吧，首先我们需要找的是地图
Okay, so the first thing we need is a map...
弄清所有出口
to figure out where all the exits are,
和警卫的巡逻地点
where the guards are located.
布鲁把地图放在他的办公室里，就在办公桌的后面
Blue has that in his office. it's behind his desk.
很好
Right. Good.
第二件东西，是用来点火了
Second thing we need is something to start a fire with...
可以在我们逃跑时，转移他们的注意力
as a distraction for when we escape.
火灾能让他们无法找到我们
Plus, the fire should disable all the checkpoints.
第三件是刀
And the third thing is a knife...
遇到问题，可以帮我们解决
in case we run into trouble.
厨师那里有
The Cook.
- 我可以拿到 - 好吧
- We can do it. - Okay.
最后一件，是钥匙
And the last thing's a key.
布鲁把钥匙戴在脖子上
Blue wears a key around his neck.
我猜是乎能打开每一扇门？
What door does it open?
是把万能钥匙，这是大关键
It's for all of them, I think. it's a master key.
这项计划太疯狂的
This plan is crazy.
到处都有警卫
There's armed guards everywhere, okay?
如果布鲁知道，我们就死定了
And if Blue finds out, we're dead.
并不能是，“抱歉，布鲁，说我们不会再犯了”
It's not gonna be, "Oh, sorry, Blue, we won't do it again."
因为我们到时已经死了
We'll be dead.
我们早就死了
We're already dead.
- 我参加 - 我也参加
- I'm in. - So am I.
我也是
Me too.
好吧
All right.
但是，我会加入，是因为没有我 你们一定会被抓到的
But I'm only doing this because you guys'd get caught without me, okay?
还有，如果有太多毛…
And if it gets too hairy...
我说如果该停手了…
if I say it's over...
我们就住手
we stop.
好吧
Okay.
我负责拿到地图
I'll get the map.
我沿着铁轨散步
I went for a walk down the railroad track.
然后你知道，一些…
Next thing you know, some...
- 怎么了？ - 她在跳舞
- What do you want? - She's dancing.
谁在跳舞？
Who is dancing?
你的宝贝豆
Your baby doll.
一颗药丸让你变大
One pill makes you larger
一颗药丸让你变小
And one pill makes you small
宝贝
Baby.
他来了 他要开始通报了
He's coming. He's gonna start the briefing.
很好，训练如下：
All right, here's the drill:
德国军队要向凯撒报告 关于地图…
The Germans are preparing a report for the kaiser. it's a map...
它标明了驻军位置和战壕布局情况
that shows troop locations and trench layouts.
他们的战地指挥官通过通信兵发送地图…
Their field commander's sending the map via courier...
就在今天通过齐柏林飞艇送回德国
back to Germany on a zeppelin today.
我们要怎么侵入领地？
How do we intercept it?
你们要穿越无人区 到达敌军阵地
You're gonna cross no man's land, enter the enemy trenches...
从指挥官的营地里 拿到地图
and take the map from the field commander's bunker...
在他们发现你们之前
before the courier can reach the zeppelin.
这听来很有趣
Sounds like fun.
我已经给安布尔安排了一些特别的东西
Oh, and I've arranged something special for Amber.
给你一些掩护
Give you some cover.
你们完成任务后马上出来
Get you out of there when you're done.
出发吧
Let's go.
你觉得怎样？
What do you think?
我乐意
I like it.
德国医生们工程师们…
German doctors and engineers...
已经在考虑他们如何着手返回前线
have worked out how to return their fallen to the front lines.
他们使用蒸汽的动力来确保它们继续工作
They're using steam power and clockworks to keep them moving.
那么别害怕，杀死他们
So don't feel bad about killing them.
他们死定了
They're already dead.
记住了，女士们：
Remember, ladies:
如果你们无所畏惧…
If you don't stand for something...
那么你们将无往不胜
you'll fall for anything.
最后一件事：
Oh, and one last thing:
注意团队作战
Try and work together.
妈的…
Son of a...
来吧，我们往这里走
Come on, guys. The bunker's this way.
- 掩护！ - 火箭女！
- Cover! - Rocket!
香豌豆！救我！
Sweet Pea! Help!
香豌豆！
Unh. Sweet Pea!
火箭女
Rocket.
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
就在这
it's right here.
火箭女 够了
Rocket. That's enough.
（你们是来拿地图，对吧？）
（千里迢迢的跑来）
（但现在你却要死了！）
（快点走！）
（把地图给我！）
（给我！）
非常好
Very good.
- 干得漂亮 - 谢谢
- Nice work. - Thanks.
非常好
Very good.
我有个主意
Okay, this gives me an idea.
让她一个人独舞怎么样？
What about a private dance for the Mayor.
什么？
What?
她随着音乐跳舞，客户们会非常喜欢
Nothing touchy-feely, just something to get him wound up.
我们借此大赚一笔
Get him ready to spend some money.
她只要像刚才那样跳就好了
All she has to do is do what she did just now.
但是她并没有准备好
这当然没问题
That is out of the question. She is not ready. It is too raw.
你说她还没准备好？
Did you just say she's not ready?
她甚至没有演出服，也没有演出场景
She doesn't have a costume. There is no set.
她跟本不需要那些，她简直是太棒了
Honey, she doesn't need that bullshit. She's perfect.
也许 可是不该由你决定，而是由我来决定
Perhaps. But that is not for you to decide, that is for me to decide.
这是我的节目，而我说她还没准备好
It's my show, and I say she's not ready.
很显然，我冒犯的你 我很抱歉
Clearly, I've offended you, and I apologize.
谢谢
Thank you.
事情是这样的：
Here's the thing:
这个节目也许是你…
This show might be yours...
但是这些女孩还有你…
but the girls and you...
都是我的
are mine.
对吗？
Right?
都是我的
You're mine.
如果你有其他意见，一定要告诉我，好吗？
And if you need a stronger reminder of that, you let me know, okay?
没有其他了
That won't be necessary.
所以不管有没有你的祝福，她明天都会上台表演，对吗？
So with or without your blessing, she's gonna be on that stage tomorrow?
- 我会尽力的 - 做得好
- I'll see what I can do. - Attagirl.
好的
All right.
顺便说一下，你看起来真棒
You look fantastic, by the way.
做得好，女孩们
Big show, girls.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 什么？ - 厨师的事
- For what? - The Cook.
- 那没什么 - 闭嘴
- It was nothing. - Shut up.
没有人会冒险，帮助这里的人
No one takes a risk for anyone in here.
所以，谢谢你
So thank you.
不客气
You're welcome.
你有家人吗？
You got family?
没有
No.
对的
Oh, that's rig ht.
我忘了，你是孤儿
I forgot, you're an orphan.
我是离家出走
I ran away from mine.
我以为这是明智之举，但是…
I thought I was pretty smart at the time, but ....
香豌豆也跟着出来
Sweet Pea followed.
挺疯狂的… 因为他跟爸爸妈妈并没有争吵
Which is crazy, because she never even had a real problem with Mom and Dad.
她是为的跟你在一起
She just cares about you a lot.
你有没有曾经想过收回一些东西呢？
Have you just ever wanted to just take something back?
收回你说的某些话
You know, something you said.
做过的某些事
Something you did.
经常
All the time.
安布尔？
Amber?
市长今晚会来
The Mayor comes tonight.
你看见没他嘴里那个雪茄烟
I've never seen him without a big stogie in his mouth.
我恨雪茄烟
Ugh. I hate those cigars.
我不想头发沾上烟味
I can never get that stink out of my hair.
- 什么？ - 是你
- What? - it's you.
- 必须拿到他的打火机 - 我不想做
- You have to get his lighter. - I'm not doing that.
- 我不能 - 你可以
- I can't. - Yes, you can.
拜托，讲道理嘛
Come on, be reasonable.
肯定还有别种方法，或别人来做这项工作
There's got to be another way, or someone else who can do it.
他是你的客户
He's your client.
如果我搞砸的怎么办？
Yeah, but what if I screw it up?
你能办妥了
You can do this.
他放在这里，你知道 在他胸部的口袋里
Well, he keeps it here, you know. In his breast pocket.
那么你就亲亲他的脖子…
So then you do the good old kiss-the-neck...
伸到衣服里…
rub-his-chest...
到达…
reach in...
目标…
and bam...
你成功了
you're gold.
没错
Yeah.
亲吻脖子
Kiss the neck.
- 他会很喜欢的 - 呵呵
- He'll like that. - Heh, heh.
不要舍弃你的幻想
Don't part with your illusions.
当他们走了，你可以继续存在，但你要停止生存
When they are gone, you may still exist, but you will cease to live.
- 谁说的？ - 马克·吐温
- Who said that? - Mark Twain.
聪明的人 你们在今晚将会很愉快
Wise man. You are going to be fine tonight.
好吧
All right.
现在…
Now...
表演时刻
showtime.
先生们 欢迎
Gentlemen. Welcome.
今晚我们为你们推荐一个新女孩 特别的女孩
We have a new girl for you tonight. Something extra special.
这是个准备中的节目…
It is a work-in-progress...
所以表演较为朴实，请大家谅解
so I apologize in advance for the raw nature of the performance.
不过，我承认…
I will say, however...
这就是她魅力的一部分
that is part of the charm.
我很荣幸的向你们介绍…
It is my pleasure to introduce to you...
宝贝豆小姐
this little baby doll.
好吧，到了准备行动
Okay. This is how it's gonna go.
安布尔你留下开飞机
Amber will keep the bird on station.
布女郎，你使用50机枪，做好掩护
Blondie, you'll operate the 50 cal here and the 30 down there.
其他人进入庭院里，杀死所有挡路的生物
The rest of you, drop into the courtyard and kill the creatures in your way.
当你们到达巢穴时，就会发现一只龙宝宝
Now, when you reach the nest, you'll find the baby.
割断它的喉咙
You'll have to slit its throat.
脖子内找两块火焰结晶
Down inside its neck are two crystals...
互相撞击两块结晶
that, when struck together,
将会产生世界上最强的火焰
produce the most magnificent fire you'll ever see.
安布尔…
Amber...
靠近城堡飞
put us on approach.
收到，马上开始
Roger that. Starting my run.
干得好！
Nice.
记住：
Remember:
想要保住你的狗命就别发出任何声音
Don't ever write a check with your mouth you can't cash with your ass.
没错… 还有最后一件
Oh, yeah, and one more thing.
别等着龙妈妈回来
Don't wake the mother.
出发！，女士们
Here we go, ladies.
前进！前进！前进！
Go! Go! Go!
前进！
Go!
上！
Up!
前进！
Go!
上！
Up!
我有办法了
I got an idea.
抓紧！
Hold on!
我抓住你了！
I got you now!
嘿！ 想报仇啊？ 妈妈！
Take that, you ugly mother.
安布尔，她在哪里？
Amber, where is she?
我没看到她
Check our 6. I don't see her.
布女郎，注意擦亮你的眼睛
Blondie, keep your eyes peeled.
我要杀…
I'll kill yo...
全看你了，宝贝
She's all yours, Baby.
不敢相信，我成功了
I can't believe I did it.
该死的，那个姑娘能跳舞
Damn, that girl can dance.
看看你能做什么？
See what you can do?
哇哦，安布尔
Wow, Amber.
看看它
Check it out.
还有一半就到家了
Halfway home.
让我看看
Let me see it.
这就像我说的：
it's just like I said:
你亲吻他的脖子，每次都见效
You kiss the neck, it works every time.
- 太好了 - 进展如何？
- Good job. - How'd we do?
太棒了 给
Nice. Here.
- 你是怎么做到了 - 你肯定想不到
- And he didn't even notice. - No. No idea.
干得好，安布尔
Good work, Amber.
- 谢谢，宝贝 - 干杯
- Thanks, Baby. - Cheers.
- 干杯 - 干杯？
- Cheers. - Cheers?
在庆祝什么？
What are we celebrating?
我该向谁道贺呢？
Who should I be congratulating?
庆祝宝贝豆第一次上舞台表演
It was just Babydoll's first time on stage.
你知道那会让人多紧张
You know how scary that can be.
为艺术家的友谊干杯？
The bond of the theater.
还是什么呢？
I mean, what else could it be?
该不会是你们之中有什么秘密吧？
I mean, it's not like any of you have anything to hide, is it?
不
No.
不会是有人在办公室…
It's not like anyone was in my office...
乱动我的东西？
messing with my shit.
不是 不像是有人丢了东西
No. it's not like people are missing things.
你们知道了，就是那些小东西
You know, small little objects here and there.
不 不，那就太荒唐了 那就太疯狂了
No. No, that would be outrageous. That would be crazy.
对吗？
Right?
因为我有一个非常明显的解释来说清楚这件事
Because we have such an obvious explanation for this exuberance.
是联谊会的表演者
It's the fraternity of performers.
It's the adrenaline from the curtain rising.
这大概是我的错
Maybe this is my fault.
也许我不该跟你们混那么熟
You know, maybe I've just become too familiar with you girls.
也许我应该给你们一个示范
Maybe I need to make an example of someone.
重新看待我们之间的关系 你们觉得怎么样？
Re-establish the parameters of our relationship. What do you think?
布女郎，姑娘们？
Blondie, girls?
还有你！
And what about you?
你觉得自己很特别，对吧？
You think you're special, don't you?
但是我要告诉你一个小秘密
Well, I'm gonna let you in on a little secret.
要不是我为了从你和豪赌客那里获得一些财产…
If I was not about to make a small fortune on you with the High Roller...
我会现在办了你并且把你的笑容…
I would take you right now and I would pop that little smile...
从你脸上扒下来
right off of your face.
让我悲剧的是不得不通过向你们发出威胁
It saddens me that I have to resort to threats with you girls.
我以为早就过的那种阶段了
I thought we were past that.
我只是… 我要这些狗屁马上停止！
I just... I need this bullshit to stop!
出于互相尊重
Gut of mutual respect.
让我们把事情回归过去
Let's get things back to how they were.
那么…
Well ....
我们结束这段试验吧
So much for that little experiment.
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
我说结束了
I'm saying it's over.
对吧，宝贝？
Right, Baby?
我不知道
I don't know.
什么"不知道"？
What do you mean, you don't know?
布鲁在观察我们
Blue's onto us.
我们有约定
We had a deal.
如果我说结束，那就结束
If I say it's over, it's over.
我们快接近成功，不能停止！
We're this close, though. We can't just stop.
你没听到布鲁说什么吗？他知道我们计划着什么
Did you not hear Blue? He knows we're up to something.
他知道我们在干什么
He knows what we're doing.
如果被当场抓住，就不会那么容易就结束了 你都看到了
If he catches us for real, it won't be a lecture. You saw him.
香豌豆，火箭女说得没错，他们明天之前不会来
Sweet Pea. Rocket is right. The High Roller comes tomorrow.
- 如果我们继续执行计划，直到那时候… - 不！你完了！
- If we can just stick with the plan till then... - No! You're screwed.
我们退出！
We're out.
火箭女…
Rocket...
我们退出了
we're out.
我会完成任务
I'm finishing this.
我们将结束这一切
We are all finishing this.
这是我们离开这里的唯一办法
You know it's the only way we can get out of here.
你要选择她…
You're gonna choose her...
一个你几乎不认识的人…
someone you barely know...
却不跟我？
over me?
在我曾经为你所做的牺牲之后
After all I've sacrificed for you.
对不起
I'm sorry.
布女郎？
Blondie?
你在这做什么？你还好吧？
What are you doing down there? Are you all right?
对不起，我没事
I'm sorry, it's nothing.
怎么了？出什么事了？是不是有人伤害你？
What? What's wrong? Did someone hurt you?
- 不，不是那样 真的没事 - 很显然…
- No, it's not like that. It's really nothing. - Clearly...
没事的
it is not nothing.
你可以告诉我，我是一个很好的听众
You can tell me. I am good listener.
高斯基夫人…
Madame Gorski...
求求你
please.
我知道这个表情
I know that look.
你觉得孤单，没人能帮助你
You think you're all alone, and that no one can help you.
但是总有解决问题的方法
There is a way to fix anything.
现在…
Now...
…告诉我发生了什么，孩子
tell me what is wrong, child.
好吧
Okay.
答应我，你会保守秘密？
Promise you can keep a secret?
- 我答应 - 我答应
- Yes. - Yes.
- 她在哪里？ - 我不知道
- Where the hell is she? - I don't know.
我们需要她的音乐
We need your music.
你知道吗？算了吧，太迟了 香豌豆是对的
You know what, forget it. No, it's too late. Sweet Pea was right.
你是什么意思？我们三人可以…
What are you talking about? The three of us, we can...
我想我们做不到了
I don't think we can do this.
我不想做一些愚蠢的事情把你们卷入危险中
I don't wanna do something stupid that's gonna put you guys in danger.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我们已经很好了 好吗？
Hey, we got this far, right?
我是说，我们做的是很多人都不能做到的
I mean, that's something not a lot of people could have done.
再说豪赌客也差不到那里去
How bad can the High Roller be, anyway?
你们没有其他事要做吗？
Don't you girls have some work you should be doing?
- 你是来帮助我们的？ - 不
- You came to help us. - No.
我来是为了保护你不被杀死
I came to keep you from getting killed.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我们没有多少时间
We don't have a lot of time.
如果你想按计行事，那么还有舞等着你跳呢
If you're done with the pleasantries, you got a dance to do.
安布尔，开始
Amber, radio.
你在干什么？
What the hell are you doing?
你会想看这个的
You're gonna wanna watch this.
停止你的思考
Turn off your mind
放松并随身心流淌
Relax and float downstream
这不是在死亡
It is not dying
放下所有思虑
Lay down all thought
投向虚空
Surrender to the void
它在闪烁
It is shining
女士们，你们今晚的任务在舞会卡上
Ladies, this is what's on our dance card for tonight.
炸弹，称为"菜刀"，去火车上盗取
The bomb, code-named "Kitchen Knife," is on a hijacked train.
约有24名武装机械人在保护
It is protected by a couple dozen mechanized gunmen.
一项简单的任务：
The idea is simple:
拿起枪打败敌人，拿到炸弹，阻止爆炸
Take care of the gunmen, deactivate the bomb, then steal it.
炸弹上的密码
The code numbers for the bomb
还有你们逃生用的喷气背包在那个行李里面
and the jetpacks for your escape are in that duffel.
知道了
Got it.
香豌豆
Sweet Pea.
我很高兴你改变了主意
I'm glad you changed your mind.
那么你也明白了
Well, there you have it.
你们奋斗的意义在于…
You know, for those who fight for it...
生活有它自己的价值，而怯懦的人永远都不会知道
life has a flavor the sheltered will never know.
最后一件事
Oh, yeah. One last thing.
装有定时器的炸弹，即将要爆炸
The bomb's timer is set to detonate when it reaches the city.
我是你们的话，就会快点行动！
So if I were you, I'd hurry!
准备好武器，女士们
Weapons hot, ladies.
搞定
Hot.
- 搞定 - 搞定
- Hot. - Hot.
锁定目标
I've got a lock.
祝好运
Good luck.
- 我们到了 - 收到
- We're down. - Copy that.
警告：
Warning:
炸弹将在4分15秒后启动
Weapon will activate in four minutes, 15 seconds.
- 警告： - 密码！
- Warning: - Codes!
炸弹将在4分10秒后启动
Weapon will activate in four minutes, 10 seconds.
警告：炸弹将在4分5秒后启动
Warning: Weapon will activate in four minutes, five seconds.
启动终止程序开始
A deactivation procedure has been initiated.
终止程序完成
Deactivation procedure complete.
炸弹被终止了
Weapon deactivated.
哦！
Whoa!
快点，安布尔 我们要把炸弹弄出来
Hurry, Amber. We gotta get this thing out of here.
来了
On my way.
请参考操作手册
Please refer to the operations manual.
细节部分在…
For details on ....
安布尔，她没事
Amber, she's good.
我带她出去
I'm taking her out.
各位，还没卸下
Guys, it's caught on something.
等等 我忘了
Hold up. We missed one.
启动重载程序完成
Override procedures complete.
炸弹已启动
Weapon active.
临近警告
Proximity warning.
安布尔，炸弹已禁用
Amber, the bomb's active.
炸弹将在35秒后爆炸
Warning: Weapon will activate in 45 seconds.
自由
Get free.
火箭女，我们走
Rocket, let's go.
炸弹将在25秒后爆炸
Weapon will activate in 25 seconds.
它坏掉没有用了
It's broke. it's not gonna work.
我不会放弃的，用我的喷射器一起走
I'm on full burn. We'll go together.
这没法承受我们两人的重量
It's not gonna carry the both of us.
- 我们得试试 - 好的 我们试试
- We have to try. - Okay, we'll try.
但你要答应我两件事
But you've gotta promise me two things.
火箭女，我们快走
Rocket, let's go.
- 第一件事… - 炸弹将在15秒后爆炸
- The first thing is... - Weapon will activate in 15 seconds.
不要生我的气
don't get mad about this.
生你什么气？
About what?
这个
This.
火箭女！
Rocket!
爆炸倒数 十，九…
Weapon will activate in 10, nine...
八，七，六…
eight, seven, six...
五，四…
five, four...
三，二，一
."three, two, one.
第二件事是…
The second thing is...
当你回家后…
when you get home...
当你自由后…
when you get free...
告诉妈妈我爱她
you tell Mom I love her.
- 我会告诉她的 - 妈妈
- I'll tell her. - Mom.
我答应你
I promise.
哦，天哪！
Oh, my.
你，你都做了什么？ 你这个大蠢猪
You, what did you do? You simple, inbred idiot.
长官，我什么都不知道，我只是…
Sir, don't know what happened. I just...
对不起 对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
快点起来！快点起来！
Get her up. Get her up, CJ!
是的，是的
Yes. Yeah, look.
你给我好好反省都做了些什么
I want you to look at what you did.
看看你做了什么！
Look at what you did, you bitch!
安布尔，亲爱的
Amber, sweetheart.
你们还要在今晚表演上找到香豌豆，快去准备
You've got Sweet Pea's slot in tonight's show. Go get ready.
去准备
Go get ready.
快去！
Go!
把她关到壁橱里去
Take her to the closet.
至于你…
As for you...
表演时间到了！
it's Showtime.
豪赌客在这里 我需要你今晚闪亮无比
The High Roller is here. I need you to focus for me.
谢谢
Ah. Thank you.
女孩们
Girls?
大家都过来一下好吗？我想说几句话
Can you just gather around for a second? I wanna say a few words.
没关系，你可以继续给她打扮
That's all right. You can just finish getting her dressed.
好的 是这样的
Okay. There we go.
非常好
Very nice.
好了
All right.
我试图给你们一个…
I try to give you all...
好的生活
a good life.
我尝试了，真的
I try. I do.
而我想要的回报只是…
And all I ask for in return is just for...
尊重
respect...
诚实
honesty.
你们知道… 没关系，玛格丽特
You know... Oh, that's okay, Margaret.
我们之间的关系
A give-and-take relationship.
却让我注意到… 让我们注意到…
But it's come to my attention... it's come to our attention...
有些老鼠屎…
that a few bad eggs...
特别是由某一个人领头…
led by one little egg in particular...
破坏了我们之间的良好信任…
have spit in the face of that generosity...
而且还想要和我作对
and are plotting against me.
我
Me.
你们的父亲
Your father.
你们的爱人
Your lover.
你们的雇主
Your employer.
密谋想要夺取我的最重要最宝贵的财产
Plotting to take from me my most precious possessions.
你太自私了
Your very selves.
布鲁，你在做什么？
Blue, what you doing?
你得到了信息 你快成功了
You got the information. You have won.
这个小女孩，将给你带来巨大的财富
This little fantasy of freedom is all they have.
不，不 没人再吃你那套了 那套不管用了，薇拉
No, no, no. No one's buying that, honey. No one's buying that, Vera.
你并不能对我做什么你们已经不能做的事情了
There is nothing you can do to me that you haven't already done.
你给我听着，老婊子
You listen to me, you old whore.
现在想装好人也太晚了，太迟了
It's too late to play the good guy. it's far too late.
你突然之间，变得不是我们之中的一个了吗？
You're suddenly not aware of what it is we do here?
我帮助她们从你手里活下来
I teach them to survive you.
- 好吧 - 对不起！我不是说要告诉任何人的
- All right. - I'm sorry! I didn't mean to say anything.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不，布女郎
No, Blondie.
我不是那个意思
I didn't mean to.
他说一切都会没事的
He said everything would be okay.
布鲁，这一切都是误解
Blue, this is a mistake.
请不要这样做，好吗？
Please don't do this, okay?
这就对了，我们亲爱的布女郎…
That's right. Our dear Blondie came to us...
只是拼命想帮她的姐妹们摆脱这种危险的道路
desperately trying to help her sisters off this most dangerous path.
刚开始，我们甚至都不相信她说的
At first, we didn't even believe her.
但是，当我听到这一切后，这一切突然变得合理了
But after hearing who was involved, frankly, it started to make sense.
- 就是这个？ - 布鲁
- Right here? - Blue.
“地图、火”
"Map. Fire."
看样子，女生们的记录有些超前的啊
Looks like that chicken was counted a little before it hatched.
我说对了吗，安布尔？
Ain't that right, Amber?
你有什么想说的吗？有吗？
You have anything to say? Anything?
布鲁，我们不是… 我们仍然…
Blue, we didn't... We were still...
没有关系的，亲爱的
You know what, sweetheart?
没关系
It's okay.
不！
NO!
- 天啊！ - 好啦，冷静点
- Oh, my God! - Okay, calm down.
这一切马上就会结束了，然后我们就能像平常那样工作了
This will all be over soon and we can get back to business as usual.
布女郎，我想要谢谢你做的一切
Blondie, I wanna thank you for everything you've done.
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
主要是，我们讨厌背叛者，所以…
The thing is, we hate snitches, so ....
不！
No!
好了，拿走吧
Okay. Here.
我讨厌武器
I hate guns.
我希望每个人都有学到有用的一课
I hope everyone's learned a valuable lesson here.
特别是你，高斯基女士 让她离开这里
Especially you, Madame Gorski. Get her out of here.
让这些闲人离开这里，好吗
Let's get these bodies out of here, please.
剩下的人，你们还要表演呢，快，快去准备吧
And the rest of you, you got a show to do. So go on, go get them, girls.
好好表演
Make it count.
我想了很多…
I've been thinking a lot...
你将带给我的那些钱
about all that money you're gonna make me.
我想了很多关于豪赌客，他的手摸遍你全身
I've been thinking a lot about the High Roller and his hands all over you.
我也想过了这儿所有其它的人…
I've been thinking about all those people out there...
他们看到你并贪恋你
just watching you and lusting after you.
你会认为那就是我最大的乐趣
And you'd think that would give me pleasure.
我是指生意上的乐趣
I mean, I'm in the business of pleasure.
但是你知道我的感觉是什么吗？
But you know what it makes me feel like?
对你说句实话，这让我觉得自己像个小男孩…
I'm gonna be honest with you. it makes me feel like I'm this little boy...
独自坐在酒吧的角落里…
sitting in the corner of the sandbox...
而其他人却在玩我的玩具…
while everybody gets to play with my toys...
但是我
but me.
我又能怎么做呢？
So you know what I'm gonna do?
我会拿回我的玩具，然后回家
I'm gonna take my toys and I'm gonna go home.
我现在回家了… 那很好！就这样了
I'm going home now... Oh, that's good! That's it.
哦，就是那样吗？！那是我的玩物
Oh, is that it'?! That's my little bitch.
你喜欢些什么呢？
This what you like?
来这里！
Come here!
什么？不不不
What? No, no, no.
来吧 来吧！
Come on. Come on!
这回是你输了吧？
Did you lose your fight? Huh?
不
No.
我只是发现了
I just found it.
你永远都别想掌控我
You'll never have me.
永远
Ever.
- 香豌豆 - 安布尔和布女郎在哪里？
- Sweet Pea. - Where's Amber and Blondie?
只有我们俩
It's just us now.
我们得走了，香豌豆，来吧！
We have to go, Sweet Pea. Come on.
- 就是这里 - 好的
- That's it. - Okay.
- 现在怎么办？ - 等着
- Now what? - Wait for it.
来吧
Come on.
该死
Damn it.
不可能的
This can't be.
我们拿到所有的东西了
We did everything right.
地图，火，刀，钥匙，还有一件东西
A map, fire, a knife, a key, and one thing more.
还有一件东西
One thing more.
是我
It's me.
什么？
What?
是我，当然是我！
Oh, it's me. Of course it's me.
只有这样才说得通
It's the only way this ever could have ended.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
我说，你回家
I'm saying you go home.
告诉你的家人
Go home to your family.
告诉你妈火箭女说过的话
You tell your mom what Rocket said.
让她高兴
Make her happy.
出去并过正常人的生活…
Go out and live a normal life...
获得爱…
love...
和自由
be free.
为我们所有的人活着
You have to live for all of us now.
- 宝贝，不，你不能那样做 - 是的，香豌豆
- Baby, no. You can't do that. - Yes, Sweet Pea.
你是最强的
You're the strongest.
你是唯一一个在外面也能过得很好的人
You're the only one of us that ever had a chance out there.
回家过正常生活就是我们的愿望
You going home and living, that's how we win.
没关系，这样更好
It's okay. it's okay. it's better this way.
现在，听着
Now listen.
我等会就走出去…
I'm gonna walk out there...
他们走向我的时候，你就快离开好吗？
and when they come after me, you go, okay?
肯定还有其他方法
There's gotta be another way.
没有
No.
这是唯一的
This is right.
这从来都不是我的故事
This was never my story.
是你的
It's yours.
别弄砸了，好吗？
Now, don't screw it up, okay?
跟着公路走，就能找到车站，好吗？
You stay off the roads and you find a bus station, all right?
你会没事的
You're gonna be fine.
你要去那里，亲爱的？
Where you going, sweetheart?
我说，你要去那里？
I said, where you going?
你醒了
There you are.
你把我们吓得不轻，知道吗？
You gave us quite a scare, you know?
我在哪里？
Where am I?
你现在安全了（此人说话忒费劲）
You're safe for now.
我不知道该如何精妙地表达，我会宽恕你的无礼…
I don't know how to put this delicately
so I will spare you the insult of being vague...
你和我应该是在OOXX的
that you and I are supposed to screw.
我希望你原谅我的表述…
I hope you'll forgive my language...
但我认为你会发现这是与协议的精神是一致的
but I think you'll find it is in keeping with the spirit of the arrangement.
现在我绝对没有任何意图来仅仅是占有你
Now I have absolutely no intention of simply taking you.
事实上…
In fact...
我不会有任何冒犯的意图
I can think of nothing more offensive.
你看到了，我就是你称之为拥有一切的那种男人
You see, I am what you might call a man who has everything.
并且我仍然缺少一件金钱买不来的东西
And yet, I lack the one thing money can't buy.
- 爱 - 有点接近
- Love? - Close.
真相…
Truth...
是更加精确的
is more accurate.
我寻求一个真实的契机，关于真相的契机
I seek a true moment, a moment of truth.
在这个…
In this...
充满谎言的世界
world of lies.
我只是碰巧遇到了…
It just so happens that...
那个契机…
that moment...
那个易碎的，像一个玻璃鸡蛋的精美工艺品一样的…
that fragile, delicate thing like a glass egg...
或者像是一个沙雕，那个契机…
or a sand castle, well, that moment...
只能被不伪装的人所展现
can only be given by a non-faker.
不演戏的人
A non-actor.
那就是你
That's you.
我不明白（靠，偶也不明白）
I don't understand.
我已经花费了…
Well, I have spent...
一小笔财富把你弄到这个房间
a small fortune getting you in this room.
这个金饰的笼子
This golden cage.
你应该把你自己奉献给我
You're supposed to give yourself to me.
这完全是物质上的
It's completely physical.
我会占有你的身体…
I might have your body...
可是真实的你却像是…
but the real you that...
不可捉摸的闪烁不定的火花，那就是你
intangible, and indefinable spark that is you.
而你永远不会知道
Well, that you I will never know.
并且我确切所想知道的就是那样了
And, yet, that is precisely what I want.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你看起来真的很完美
You seem really nice.
你想让我对你撒谎吗？
You want me to lie to you?
不，我不要
No, I don't.
我对你所有的索求…
All I require from you...
就是一丝的契机
is a sliver of a moment.
就是不用暴力拥有你…
To have you not by force...
而是像男人和女人之间那样简单
but simply as a man and a woman.
从你眼中看到的简单真相…
To see in your eyes that simple truth...
你所给出你自己的真相让我无拘无束
that you give yourself to me freely.
不是因为你必须…
Not because you have to...
而是以为你想要
but because you want to.
现在呢，像你这样的珍品…
Now, of course, you're such a gem...
我同样的会给予
I will give as well.
我愿意给你自由
I'm willing to give you freedom.
纯粹的完全的自由
Pure and total freedom.
免于每天苦工一样的生活…
Freedom from the drudgery of every day life...
就像抽象概念一样的自由
freedom as abstract ideal.
免于痛苦…
Freedom from pain...
免于责任…
freedom from responsibility...
免于罪行…
freedom from guilt...
免于忏悔…
from regret...
免于悲伤…
freedom from sadness...
免于失去…
freedom from loss...
自由地去开心
the freedom to be happy.
别闭上眼睛
Don't close your eyes.
我要你看着我
I need you to look at me.
爱的自由
The freedom to love.
耶稣啊
Jesus.
你看到她看着我的样子吗？
Did you see the way she looked at me?
就是最后那一刻，就好像？
Just in that last moment. It was like ....
医生？
Doctor?
结束了吗？
Is it done?
高斯基医生，你知道她吗？
Dr. Gorski, what do you know about this one?
我只是很奇怪
Uh, there was something very peculiar.
当然，她妈妈因病过世，在这种压力下
Yes. Her mother's death plunged her into a deep depression.
然后她失手杀死了她的妹妹
And then in a fit, she accidentally killed her sister.
可怜的孩子
Poor child.
很遗憾，我们不能为她做得更多
It's a shame I couldn't do more for her.
我也没有太多的权利，你知道的
I wasn't given much time, you see.
是的，但是你推荐了这个手术
Yes, but you recommended the procedure.
我很抱歉，我没有
Oh, I'm afraid not.
我觉得她很不好管理
I will admit she has been quite a handful.
只是在这一周时间，她就刺伤了护理员，放了一场火…
In just one week here, she stabbed an orderly, started a fire...
还帮助其他的病人逃跑
and helped another patient to escape.
但是我并不同意这样的手术，医生
But I don't agree with this solution, doctor.
但是，你为什么会为一个你不同意的手术签字呢？
But why would you sign for a procedure you don't agree with?
那是你的签名，对吧？
That is your signature, is it not?
我做这种手术很多次了，医生…
I've been doing this for quite some time, doctor...
我跟你说实话
and to be honest with you,
我并不觉得我们有这权利
I've wondered myself whether or not it's right.
就是在虐待被俘的战士一样，相信我
And I have seen some tortured souls in here. Believe me.
但是这一个…
But this one ....
在她眼中有某样东西
Something in her eyes.
我从来也没有见过有谁像她这样
I've never seen anyone that ....
他的那个表情
it's the way she looked at me.
就好像她很希望我这样做
It's like she wanted me to do it.
希望一切顺利
I hope it helps her.
嗨！
Hi.
你还记得我吗？
You remember me?
听着，我有一种不好的感觉
Listen. Listen, I got a bad feeling, okay?
这些家伙也是
These boys do too.
我们不应该以这种方式管理这里
This is not the way we should be running this place.
不是我们管理这里，是我管理
We don't run the place. I run it.
放在椅子上
In the chair.
听着…
Look...
我不…
I'm not....
- 我不会再伤害这个女孩了 - 我不会这么做的
- I'm not hurting these girls anymore. - I'm not doing this.
各位，别这样对我，拜托了
Guys, don't do this to me now, please.
我要让她坐在椅子上
I need her in that chair.
坐在那个该死的椅子上！
Put her in the goddamn chair!
谢谢
Thank you.
请关上门
Close the door, please.
怎么？、怎么了，你不在这里吗？
What? What is it, you're not here? Huh?
你不在这里了吗？你到天堂去了吗？
You're not here, you're in paradise? No, no, no. No, no, no.
不，不，不
No, no, no.
你还是在这里
You're still here.
你在这里和我一起
You're here with me.
该死！
In all this shit.
你不能走，除非我答应
And you don't go away unless I say so.
好吧？
Okay?
这样不对
That's not right.
回来
Come back.
不不！
No! No!
我说你不许走！
I said you don't go!
你这样对待我
You come back to me.
- 住手 离开那位姑娘 - 你在做什么？
- Stop right there. Move away from the girl. - What are you doing?
等等、等等、等等…
Aah! Wait. Wait. Wait, wait, wait. Wait. Aah!
上帝啊，你究竟对她做了什么？
What in God's name have you been doing up here?
我什么都没做，你看看她
I wasn't doing anything. Look at her.
她已经死了，看看她的脸，她已经不在了
She's gone. Look at her face! She's not here.
你觉得我还能做什么？我照顾这些女孩
What do you think I wanna do? I take care of these girls.
我看护她们，她们是我的 告诉他们
I look out for them. These are my girls. Tell them.
告诉他们！
Tell them!
把他带走
Get him out of here.
- 马上 - 等等、等等……
- Now. - Wait. Wait, wait, wait! Wait.
我不是你们想要的，是她的继父
It's not me you want, it's her stepfather.
我会告诉你们所有事的，我会告诉你们…
I'll tell you everything. I'll tell you...
我会告诉你们关于钱的事
I'll tell you about the money.
一直走到大厅里
Just keep going down the hall.
你没事吧，女士？
You all right, miss?
女士？
Miss?
最后，这个问题：
And finally, this question:
到底是谁的神秘故事…
The mystery of whose story it will be...
是谁放下最后的幕布
of who draws the curtain.
是谁为我们设定台上的舞步？
Who is it that chooses our steps in the dance?
是谁让我们疯狂…
Who drives us mad...
用皮鞭击打我们…
lashes us with whips...
当我们成为不可能的最后幸存者又让我们称王？
and crowns us with victory when we survive the impossible?
到底是谁…
Who is it...
掌控着所有这些？
that does all these things?
往南去韦恩堡的22路公交车现在开始发车了
Bus 22 southbound to Fort Wayne will now begin loading.
请拿着你们的车票准备给司机检查
Please have your tickets ready to show the driver.
打扰了，女士
Excuse me, miss?
女士，我们能谈谈吗？
Miss, can we have a word?
有什么问题吗，先生们？
Is there a problem, gentlemen?
这和你没有关系，我们在问这位年轻的女士
This doesn't concern you. I have questions for the lady.
好的，但是你们可以快点吗？，我要按时发车
Well, could you make it snappy? I need to stay on schedule.
- 我们理解 - 是吗？
- We understand. - Do you?
这位年轻女士自从哈特福就上车了
That young woman's been on this bus since Hartford.
我不觉得她会知道
I don't see what she could possibly know
这里发生的任何事情
about anything happening around here.
是真的吗？
Is that true, miss?
我刚让她下车去了趟洗手间 我车上的坏了
I just let her off to use the restroom. Mine's not working.
- 好吧 - 哦，还有最后一件事
- All right. - Oh, and one more thing.
- 她整个旅途都很愉快 - 是的，我说了，好吧
- She's been a joy the entire journey. - Yes, I said, all right.
对不起给你带来不便，我们祝您旅途愉快
Sorry about the inconvenience, miss. You have yourself a nice trip now.
没关系
It's no problem.
- 我并没有车票 - 我知道，没有关系
- I don't have a ticket. - I know. it's okay.
去后面找个位置坐下吧 试图睡一会
Go find a seat in the back. Try and get some sleep.
我们还有很长的路要走…
We got a long way to go.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谁是我们一生中所爱的人？
Who honors those we love with the very life we live?
谁派了怪兽来杀害我们…
Who sends monsters to kill us...
但是我们却依旧能够存活下来？
and at the same time sings that we'll never die?
谁告诉我们什么是真的以及笑对谎言？
Who teaches us what's real and how to laugh at lies?
谁决定我们为何而生以及我们为谁而死？
Who decides why we live and what we'll die to defend?
谁改变了我们？
Who chains us?
谁掌握着带给我们自由的钥匙？
And who holds the key that can set us free?
是你
It's you.
你拥有你所需要的一切武器
You have all the weapons you need.
现在，战斗吧！
Now Fight.